cable.co.uk 2019-02-02

# Privacy Policy

Cable.co.uk only retains personal information which relates to subscriptions to email notifications and/or newsletters. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our subscribers; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. 

Data Controller means the person or organisation who determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data is processed. We, Existent Limited are the Data Controller. 

## What information do we collect?

When you visit and use this website we may collect, temporarily store and use the following kinds of data: 

  1. anonymised information about visits to and use of this website (including browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views); 
  2. anonymised information relating to any transactions carried out between visitors and us on or in relation to this website, including anonymous information relating to any purchases subsequently made; 
  3. information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters (including your email address); 
  4. helping you obtain vouchers for deals that you have bought through our web-site;
  5. any other information that you choose to send to us;

Our legal basis for handling your personal information is therefore for the purposes of our legitimate interests in ensuring you receive from us the services you have asked us to provide. 

## Cookies

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. 

We may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and other uses. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit; and other uses. 

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date. 

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html. 

Our advertisers/payment services providers may also send you cookies. 

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one. 

## Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites. 

## Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. We take your privacy and the security of your personal information extremely seriously, and we comply with the requirements of the GDPR. 

We will only use your personal information to: 

  1. send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
  2. send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);
  3. deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;
  4. help you get offer vouchers from third parties that you have bought through our web-site, although we do not store any of your personal information.
  5. If you have any queries relating to our use of your personal data or any other data protection or privacy policy issues then please contact us on privacy@cable.co.uk or by writing to us at:

Complaints  
Existent Ltd  
53 Wade Street  
Lichfield WS13 6HL 

## Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers (including their sub-contractors) or our subcontractors insofar as is necessary for the purposes of providing our services to you and on the understanding they keep the information confidential and in accordance with the terms set out in this privacy policy. This will include, but not be limited to, any third party we use for the provision to us of a marketing platform. 

In addition, we may disclose information about you: 

  1. to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
  2. in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
  3. in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and
  4. to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties. 

## Transferring your information outside of Europe

We currently do not transfer your personal data outside the EEA. If in the future we transfer your personal data, in accordance with the terms of this Policy outside of the EEA, we will make sure that the party receiving the data agrees to provide the same or similar protection that we do and that the information they receive is used only in accordance with our instructions. 

## Marketing

We would like to send you information about services and products of ours [and other companies in our group] which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. 

You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to other members of our group. 

If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please email privacy@cable.co.uk.

## Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password. 

## Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

## Your rights

The GDPR grants you the right to access particular personal data that we hold about you. 

You therefore have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at the following address: Existent Ltd, 53 Wade Street, Lichfield, WS13 6HL.. 

We shall respond promptly to any such request and in any event, within one month from the point of receiving the request and all necessary information from you. In certain (very limited) circumstances, we may make a small charge for this service. Our formal response will include details of the Personal Data we hold about you, including the following: 

  * Sources from which we acquired the information;
  * The purposes for Processing; and
  * The persons or entities with whom we are sharing the information.

You also have the right to receive your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and have the right to ask us to transmit it to another controller if technically possible. 

We want to make sure that your Personal Data is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove without delay any information about you that you think is inaccurate by emailing us at privacy@cable.co.uk or writing to us at the above address. 

You have the right to seek a restriction of the processing of your Personal Data in certain circumstances. Further, you have the right to lodge an objection if you feel that one of the grounds relating to your particular situation apply. When you exercise your right to object, we must stop any processing unless we can show compelling legitimate grounds for the Processing, which override your interest, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims. 

Should you wish for us to completely delete all information that we hold about you, you should please contact privacy@cable.co.uk. 

## Data retention 

We will keep your personal information only for as long as we need. 

## Complaints

If you feel that your personal data has been processed in a way that does not comply with the GDPR, you have a specific right to lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority. The supervisory authority will then inform you of the progress and outcome of your complaint. The supervisory authority in the UK is the Information Commissioner’s Office. 

## Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to privacy@cable.co.uk or by post to Complaints, Existent Ltd, 53 Wade Street, Lichfield, WS13 6HL.
